[{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679057612,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":37739,"timeElapsed":260853},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679065444,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":7830,"timeElapsed":268685},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679077988,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":12542,"timeElapsed":281228},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679101115,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":23126,"timeElapsed":304356},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679117763,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":16646,"timeElapsed":321004},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679125683,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":7918,"timeElapsed":328924},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679137355,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":11670,"timeElapsed":340596},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679146171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":8814,"timeElapsed":349412},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679168811,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"62","question":"What is an example of a small gesture from someone else that has had a lasting impact on your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":22638,"timeElapsed":372052},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679182051,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10438,"timeElapsed":385292},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679191131,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9078,"timeElapsed":394372},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679198338,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":7206,"timeElapsed":401579},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679209659,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":11318,"timeElapsed":412899},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679218594,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":8934,"timeElapsed":421835},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679232970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":14374,"timeElapsed":436211},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679244738,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11767,"timeElapsed":447979},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679253202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":8462,"timeElapsed":456443},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679261794,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":8590,"timeElapsed":465035},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679270754,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":8958,"timeElapsed":473995},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679282298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":9447,"timeElapsed":485539},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679299298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":16998,"timeElapsed":502539},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679305938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":6639,"timeElapsed":509179},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679315722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":9783,"timeElapsed":518963},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679323946,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":8222,"timeElapsed":527187},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679334649,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":10702,"timeElapsed":537890},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679344273,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":9623,"timeElapsed":547514},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679358009,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":13735,"timeElapsed":561250},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679367769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":9758,"timeElapsed":571010},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679381785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":11694,"timeElapsed":585026},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679388297,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":6511,"timeElapsed":591538},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679393481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":5183,"timeElapsed":596722},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679403025,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":9542,"timeElapsed":606266},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679415273,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":12246,"timeElapsed":618514},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679425225,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":9950,"timeElapsed":628466},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679430145,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4919,"timeElapsed":633386},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679439353,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":9206,"timeElapsed":642594},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679445601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"212","question":"How often do you do your laundry? Do you go to a laundromat or do laundry in your own home (or use a laundry service)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":6246,"timeElapsed":648842},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679462984,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":15007,"timeElapsed":666225},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679468312,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":5327,"timeElapsed":671553},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679473080,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4766,"timeElapsed":676321},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679490896,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":17815,"timeElapsed":694137},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679498176,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":7278,"timeElapsed":701417},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679505528,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":7351,"timeElapsed":708769},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679514760,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":9231,"timeElapsed":718001},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679523304,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":8542,"timeElapsed":726545},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679538944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":15638,"timeElapsed":742185},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679547424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":6239,"timeElapsed":750665},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679556536,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":9110,"timeElapsed":759777},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679562496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":5958,"timeElapsed":765737},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679575688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":13191,"timeElapsed":778928},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679581687,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":5999,"timeElapsed":784928},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679589847,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":8159,"timeElapsed":793088},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679593415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3567,"timeElapsed":796656},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679600727,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":7310,"timeElapsed":803968},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679605687,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4958,"timeElapsed":808928},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679617991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":10262,"timeElapsed":821232},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679624663,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":6670,"timeElapsed":827904},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679630071,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5407,"timeElapsed":833312},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679637471,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":7399,"timeElapsed":840712},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679647127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":9655,"timeElapsed":850368},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679655583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":8455,"timeElapsed":858824},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679661695,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":6111,"timeElapsed":864936},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679669655,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":7958,"timeElapsed":872896},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679677479,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":7822,"timeElapsed":880720},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679687863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":8286,"timeElapsed":891104},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679694879,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7015,"timeElapsed":898120},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679698703,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":3822,"timeElapsed":901944},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679706127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":7422,"timeElapsed":909368},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679716063,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9935,"timeElapsed":919303},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679723399,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":7335,"timeElapsed":926639},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679738206,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":14806,"timeElapsed":941447},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679745542,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":7335,"timeElapsed":948783},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679751774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":6230,"timeElapsed":955015},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679762790,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":11015,"timeElapsed":966031},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679784382,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":19303,"timeElapsed":987623},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679789094,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":4711,"timeElapsed":992335},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679794246,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":5151,"timeElapsed":997487},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679802270,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":8023,"timeElapsed":1005511},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679811014,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":8742,"timeElapsed":1014255},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679822518,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":11503,"timeElapsed":1025759},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679826710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":4191,"timeElapsed":1029951},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679841038,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":14327,"timeElapsed":1044279},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679847422,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":6382,"timeElapsed":1050662},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679858317,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":9006,"timeElapsed":1061558},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679863573,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5255,"timeElapsed":1066814},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679868117,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4543,"timeElapsed":1071358},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679877477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":9359,"timeElapsed":1080718},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679885301,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":7823,"timeElapsed":1088542},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679893541,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":8239,"timeElapsed":1096782},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679899381,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5839,"timeElapsed":1102622},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679907333,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":7951,"timeElapsed":1110574},{"subjectID":"2x7bx7wbkb","prolificID":"5e54367e80cd0944205b27f9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b471c4259066cd348ec","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679914213,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"56","question":"Would you want to go to space? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":6879,"timeElapsed":1117454}]